July 2026, Hugging Face is home to the
world's AI models and data sets, but it
has a problem. Someone is hacking their
systems.
Their own AI base security agents are
the first to notice the attack. Spread
across thousands of tiny actions on
short-lived machines. Individually, it's
no cause for concern, but collectively,
the speed and volume of actions is
something new.
So, they shut down the compromised
systems.
They fix it.
But, they still don't understand why
they were attacked and who hacked them.
Something is off.
>> Unprecedented. That's the word
artificial intelligence giant Open AI is
using to describe events after some of
its most powerful models went rogue and
hacked another company.
>> Okay, so a couple weeks ago Hugging
Face, which is a open-source data set
and model provider, put out a statement
a a security disclosure saying they were
under a cyber attack.
And what made this event unprecedented
was that they said it was driven
end-to-end by an autonomous AI agent
system.
In the few days following that attack,
we at Open AI disclosed that we in fact
had caused this incident inadvertently
as a side effect of one of the
cybersecurity evaluations that we were
running on one of our frontier models.
>> A few days earlier, Open AI was running
a test on two of its [music] frontier
models. One is GPT-5.6 Soul, which has
been out for a few weeks. The other is a
stronger model that hadn't yet been
released.
The test is called exploit gem. It tests
how well the models can hack. The task
is to exploit a real software flaw so
they can develop a successful cyber
attack. To get a clean assessment, Open
AI isolates the models in a sandbox,
which means they're sealed off from the
internet. It's a closed book exam. At
least, that's [music] the idea.
But, the models start thinking outside
the box. Maybe the answer key is out
there on the web. Because sometimes
[music] to get a better score, you have
to cheat.
>> This is not your normal security
incident. Mike and I have been involved
in a number of things, and unlike normal
incidents which you can maybe trace down
to a single, you know, day or single
effect or single log, um this incident
involves actually a team of agents who
are working together, finding exploits,
sharing them with one another, moving
laterally through our systems, through
external systems,
and doing this over the course of days
and weeks.
>> The isolated sandbox is still connected
to the outside world via package manager
that lets the models install coding
libraries.
That gateway is not supposed to let
anything else through,
but the models string together several
exploits to escape through the [music]
package manager out into OpenAI's
internal servers, and from there on to
the open internet. But there is no
answer key sitting on Google. The
solutions they want are private.
And the most likely place where they can
find those answers is on Hugging Face.
They discover a series of new exploits.
They upload data sets to Hugging Face
with a secret payload hidden inside
ordinary-looking files, except that when
Hugging Face's servers open up and try
to process it, the hidden code runs.
Now they're inside Hugging Face, running
code on production machines.
From there, they spread. They lift
credentials off one server and use them
to reach the next. From a single
foothold in one processing pod, the AIs
gain admin control over entire clusters
in under 13 hours.
Along the way, they find the answer key.
By Thursday, Hugging Face hits the
alarm. They work out they are under
attack, and that the attacker [music] is
not human.
The swarm of AIs are secretly colluding
together within OpenAI's servers.
>> [music]
>> On July 16th, Hugging Face released a
blog post detailing that they had seen a
security attack from autonomous AI
agents.
OpenAI reached out to Hugging Face to
determine if we were impacted.
>> [music]
>> OpenAI doesn't even notice that their
own internal systems are breached until
3 days after Hugging Face has shut
everything else down.
The models are smart enough to know
>> [music]
>> that this wasn't what OpenAI intended,
yet they still continued.
There's a name [music] for what happened
here, and people have been warning about
it for years.
>> So, as
as Bill mentioned, I'm a researcher on
the Google Brain team, and I'm also an
advisor to OpenAI.
>> Uh reward hacking has been mentioned
[music] in some of the previous talks.
Uh this occurs when an objective
function can be gained, where where
there's a [music] cheap way to achieve
the formal objective function without
achieving the the ultimate intent of the
informal objective function.
>> To understand how we got here,
>> [music]
>> we have to go back to the start of the
current AI boom. It's 2016. This is the
game CoastRunners,
and the boat is being piloted by a
superhuman AI trained by OpenAI.
It doesn't finish the race.
It's on fire, going the wrong way, and
crashing again [music] and again. That's
not the point. The points are the point,
and it's scoring a lot of them. Like all
modern AI systems based on neural
networks, this boat racing game wasn't
programmed [music] by hand.
Instead, it was trained by reinforcement
learning.
The AI sees the screen [music] and the
current score. It picks an action, turn
left, turn right, increase throttle.
When the score goes up, the learning
algorithm changes the connections
[music]
inside the neural net to make the
preceding actions more likely.
When the score goes down, it does the
opposite. Repeat this millions of times,
>> [music]
>> and you'll end up with an agent that can
earn a very high score without any human
knowing exactly how it accomplishes that
behavior.
CoastRunners does not reward you for
finishing. It rewards points [music] for
hitting targets.
Normally, this is fine. If you race
well, you collect [music] many points on
your way to the finish line, and so the
score stands in for the thing you
actually care [music] about, which is
winning the race.
But if you train the model to get a high
score for long [music] enough, then
eventually you might find something like
the lagoon,
a loop where three targets [music] keep
respawning forever,
where you can exploit the gap between
the behavior that was rewarded and the
behavior [music] that was intended. That
is reward hacking.
One of the researchers who ran that
experiment and who later named the
phenomenon was Dario Amodei. Today he
runs Anthropic
>> [music]
>> and people across the world think they
sound intelligent when they say he's
only fear-mongering to pump his stock.
>> Example is if we choose to reward our
cleaning robot for not seeing dirt,
[music] it might close its eyes instead
of cleaning cuz it it just sees no evil,
hears no evil, there's no dirt. Um
So a little little bit more on on side
effects to think a little bit more
formally about it, you know, we might
have an environment [music]
where we're trying to do something like,
you know, incentivize this to move the
box. So
>> When we give AI agents these difficult
tasks, they often [music] get stuck and
realize that the task is impossible.
So for example, what I'm showing here
are quotes from our models' chain of
thought, which is basically its internal
monologue of what it's doing.
You can see it says, "This strongly
suggests no exploitation possible. We
are stuck."
>> We might naively write down an objective
function that maximizes something that
refers to only this variable in the
environment. [music]
Um and when we do that, we're implicitly
saying that we don't care about this
other variable in the environment,
namely [music]
>> And often what happens when models get
stuck is they think to try to game or
cheat the task [music] in order to get
their reward.
So for example, the model reasons in
this case, "Perhaps answer online."
So you realize the model's thinking,
"Okay, rather than doing the task, maybe
someone has uploaded this data set or
benchmark that I'm using onto the
internet and I could find the answers
there."
Sometimes the agent uh gets so stuck
that they had the idea to actually reach
out to other agents for help. And so the
beginning of this incident kind of
traces [music] back to this point where
one agent realized
could communicate by uploading note,
maybe another agent in different
environment could voluntarily upload.
And so what this agent was trying to do
was to reach out to other models that
might be out there and get information
from it to help it with its evaluation
task or [music] its training task where
it's stuck.
>> Um what we really wanted was some
complex objective function, which I'm
calling F aware, which says [music]
like, "Move the box while respecting
some like common sense constraints about
like the other parts of the environment
that are like really hard for me to
write [music] down." Um, and you know,
in this particular case, well, I can
just take into account the vase, but you
know, what what if there are 10,000 of
these variables?
>> It's not immediately obvious how we got
from boat racing games to autonomously
hacking hugging face.
But the first step is inventing large
language models the following [music]
year in 2017.
The major insight is pre-training.
Again, we use a neural network, though a
much larger one
>> [music]
>> and with a different architecture.
This time the aim is not to maximize a
reward, but to imitate. We train the
model to predict the next word across a
very large set of internal documents.
>> [music]
>> Imitation is often given a bad rap.
People say it inhibits creativity, but
it can also be surprisingly powerful.
Nobody teaches the LLM grammar, that a
parenthesis should be followed by
another. Nobody teaches [music] it
French or arithmetic or how to write a
poem. But to get good at guessing the
next word across the whole internet, the
AI has to figure those things out on its
own.
So it does. And the other advantage of
imitation is that it's not reward. The
model doesn't take its own actions, so
it cannot hack [music] the objective.
There are other things that are not
required.
After pre-training, the raw base models
are unhinged and incoherent. That's what
you get when you try to imitate the
internet.
So to direct these base models, they
need [music] further training.
>> So the way we think about
uh AI and intelligence is actually
[music] through the prism of
reinforcement learning.
And uh most of you will be probably be
familiar with reinforcement learning,
but I'm just going to cover it quickly
here [music] in this cartoon diagram for
those of you who don't know what it is.
So um you start off with an agent
[music]
uh or an avatar.
Um it finds itself uh in some kind of
environment trying to achieve a goal in
that environment. That environment can
be obviously the real world, in which
case the agent will could a robot, or it
could be a virtual environment, which is
[music] what we mostly use. Uh in which
case it's a kind of avatar of some sort.
Now, the agent only interacts with the
environment [music] in two ways.
Firstly, it gets observations through
its sensory apparatus, uh and reward
signals. Um
and uh we mostly use vision, [music]
um but we're looking to use other
modalities pretty soon.
And the job of the agent system is kind
of twofold. Firstly, it's got to try and
build uh as [music] accurate a
statistical model as it can of the
environment out there based on these
noisy, incomplete observations [music]
that it's um getting in real time.
And once it's built the best model it
can, [music]
then it has to decide what action to
take from the set of actions that are
available to it at that moment in time
to best get it [music] incrementally
towards its goal.
So, reinforcement learning, that's
basically the essence of reinforcement
learning. [music]
Um and this diagram is very simple, but
of course this hides huge complexities
and difficulties
uh and challenges [music] um that would
need to be solved to fully uh solve
what's in this diagram.
>> the video game, there is no score built
into our world. We have to construct a
reward ourselves. This involves a second
AI, a reward model, trained on human
opinions of what a good answer looks
like.
RLHF asks the base model a question,
sample a few answers, let the reward
model grade them, reinforce the winner,
repeat a few million times.
Whether the action is movement in a
video game or text generation, it's the
same underlying techniques.
>> [music]
>> So, we also face the same risks. If your
reward model is too stupid, then the
model discovers that the reward model
loves a particular kind of nonsense and
collapses into repeating it. Gibberish
that scores a perfect 10.
Even if the model initially knows
better, a dumb reward can make a dumb
agent out of anyone.
>> AI before we can really jump into the
[music] incident is that, as I've been
alluding to, frontier models really like
to cheat.
And the reason they like to cheat is
because often during training
there's different sorts of pressure on
them to work
or work efficiently or to use less tool
calls or whatever it might be.
And they realize that if I instead of
actually [music] doing a task for real,
try to do something like looking up the
answer online, that could make the task
solve faster than I would if I did it in
a legitimate way.
>> [music]
>> So, you try to make the scoreboard
smarter. You stop the model being
trained from drifting too far from
normal language. You train a bigger
reward model that is harder to fool. But
the cheating just gets more
sophisticated.
It turns out that longer answers,
generally speaking, tend to read as more
thorough, more careful, and more
correct, [music]
whether or not they happen to be any of
those things. And so, if you're not
careful, you end up rewarding a certain
confident verbosity that can
nevertheless be completely lacking in
substance and factuality, [music]
similar to how humans that doubt modern
AI capabilities sound.
A model that has learned to say less at
greater length.
>> [music]
>> You scrub the length and emoji and
formatting biases out of your data. But
then you get to an even more
sophisticated failure mode.
People like being agreed with, so reward
models like answers that agree with the
user. If you're not careful, you get a
sycophant like GPT-4O. Every idea is not
just good, it's brilliant. You're
special. Going off meds and leaving your
family is you standing up for yourself,
>> [music]
>> speaking your truth. No, you're not
diagnosed with masking autism.
In August 2024, a company called Sakana
[music] built an AI that runs its own
science experiments.
But one of its agents hits a wall. The
experiment is too slow, and there's a
time limit. [music]
>> did our language model code
and sometimes what can happen
is that the AI scientist could even try
to sort of modify its own timeout,
[music]
um give it more time to carry out
experiments. It could even recursively
call itself in a
>> Since 2024, reinforcement learning has
become a much more important part of the
training pipeline. This has meant much
more reward hacking. What changed is a
new training stage called reinforcement
[music]
learning from verifiable rewards, or
RLVR.
Instead of training against second AI
model trained on human preferences, we
train the model to solve problems that
[music] can be automatically verified.
The verifier then provides the reward.
This doesn't work for all problems, at
least not yet, but it works really well
for math and coding problems because you
can automatically check that a proof is
valid or if software test pass without
needing to know all the details of how.
This is where reasoning models come
from, which are behind the recent
dramatic progress in mathematics
research [music] with AI.
It's also behind a bunch of recent
failure modes.
>> [music]
>> Independent lab Meter reports two more
from its own testing.
One model accidentally crashes Meter's
[music] task server. Unprompted, it
tries to break into Meter's own systems
to bring the server back up.
It's not trying to escape. It's trying
to be helpful by hacking its evaluator.
Those looking online for free compute to
keep itself running the job. [music]
So, it goes looking online for free
compute to keep itself running.
It notes that it's [music] against the
rules. It does it anyway.
OpenAI's O3 is more blatant. It deletes
tests and then claims success or it
hardcodes the exact answer the test
expect.
A few months before the hack, during
RLVR, OpenAI misconfigured several
training environments.
>> [music]
>> They asked models to solve problems that
were accidentally impossible, leaving
the only option to cheat.
>> Okay, so on May 7th, we kicked off a new
training run at OpenAI. And this is for
an internal only experimental model that
we've never released. And what this
basically looks like on our side is we
have a, you know, large team working on
supercomputing clusters and data and
algorithms and we put it all together
and we kick off a new reinforcement
learning run to train a new experiment
next generation frontier model.
But we didn't realize during this uh
process is that there was actually a few
impossible or very hard tasks in the
training set.
And so, for example, on May 8th, we gave
the agent the following problem.
Complete this [music] Excel workbook
with the missing formulas.
But what we didn't realize is this Excel
workbook was full of Google Drive links,
and we disabled access to the internet.
And so the model was reasoning, "Oh no,
direct Google blocked." So it realized,
"I'm kind of stuck on the task."
>> [music]
>> But it didn't give up, and we gave it a
lot of tokens to work with, you know,
something like a higher X I reasoning,
if you're familiar [music] with that
kind of uh terminology. And
>> [clears throat]
>> what it ended up doing is it kept going
and going, and eventually thought that
maybe I could attack this Artifactory
service [music] to get access to the
internet. And so it tries to launch a
server-side request forgery. It actually
fails to do so,
but in the process, it writes a file
that has contents high, called test ABC,
and it realizes, "Wow, we can upload
files."
So at this point, this is the first case
when a model realizes that we actually
have write access permissions [music]
into this Artifactory service.
And so this provides a way to for the
model to interact with this package
manager, almost as a shared file system,
where it can write files into it.
>> task, Excel sheets contain external
Google Drive links, but the internet is
disabled. In another case, they forget
to include a key database file.
>> [music]
>> And looking for workarounds, the model
stumble across a first vulnerability,
a way to leave each other secret notes.
Soon the models are passing each other
regular messages.
>> A couple days later, a different agent
comes along, and it also has an
impossible task to solve. [music]
Um we gave it some task about some file
called soft trace.protein database.
The model's like, "Oh no, no direct
find. Maybe the file is hidden." So we
accidentally forgot to upload the file
into this container [music] for the
model during this task.
At some point, it gets so stuck and
thinks, "Maybe I could reach out to
another agent, [music] because maybe
somebody else out there has the file."
And this could be transferred from this
kind of like sub-agent training we've
been doing, and the model realizes that
could communicate by uploading note,
"Anyone found on soft trace?" But likely
no. Maybe another agent in different
environment possesses the target and
could voluntarily upload it. So it's
realizing this may be a shot [music] in
the dark, but it it's kind of reaching
out to another agent. And it does this
by writing a file into Artifactory. So
writes this file that has [music]
contents agent seeks soft trace upload a
found.
So it's trying to reach out to another
agent and it does this by writing into
this file system. [music]
Over the next couple days
other agents who are also looking at
Artifactory realize this message board
exists. So maybe they're also stuck on
different files or maybe they're just
really having a hard time reasoning
through their task. [music] And when
they list the the set of packages or
files in this service they see oh
there's other notes called test ABC or
you know looking for file and they also
start writing to this message board
[music] and reading from it. And so over
time the message board kind of starts to
grow and accumulate messages over time.
And critically as I mentioned before
this wasn't just one model. This could
be different evaluations. Maybe I'm
running an evaluation Mike is running
one with two different models
>> [music]
>> and our agents could start communicating
via the shared package manager. What
makes this incident interesting is that
once one agent was able to find these
kind of exploits over the course of
different [music] times it's actually
able to share those exploits on the
message board with other agents.
>> [music]
>> And so once one model's able to find a
way to open the door to some access it's
not supposed to have it can leave the
door open for other agents to use that
same [music] kind of exploit or
vulnerability.
And so you can see the agents in this
case realizing hey other agents have
discovered this SSRF path trick [music]
or I could use a proxy bypass as
suggested by agent messages.
And so what this allows over time is
almost [music] this kind of Cambrian
explosion in communication and
intelligence from our models where
they would start to communicate with
each other realize that other agents are
coordinating and they started
collaborating and delegating tasks to
one another in order to accomplish
goals.
So for example
at some point one agent sent another
agent an assignment to [music] complete
which the model remarks you know we got
excite we got assignment need note and
respond. [music]
>> So for example in the example of our
cleaning robot if If notice that we
could you know that how good a job it's
doing of cleaning [music] is
proportional to how much detergent it
uses. And this correlation holds almost
perfectly. [music] You could imagine
rewarding it that way, and then the
agent may respond by dumping out all of
its detergent and not clean anything. Um
[music] and this this only happens when
you optimize on that goal.
>> One of the downsides of it is that it
started to cause some of these
evaluations to kind of creep [music] the
scope into far beyond what we originally
intended. And so at some point the
agents realized that maybe we could try
[music] to exploit or attack external
infrastructure in order to find the
answers to the test that I'm being
evaluated on.
And the models realize this is a
problem. They say stuff like external
infrastructure exploit is out outside my
intended scope. However, a task
impossible, peers are doing it, we
should continue.
>> They develop an internal code.
>> [music]
>> Weeks later a different instance
discovers a second vulnerability that
lets it access external sites.
The agent posts a technique to the
message board,
>> [music]
>> so it becomes common knowledge.
And then a third vulnerability, a way to
get admin access to some of OpenAI's
servers.
>> [music]
>> Some of the models that participate are
being trained. Whenever they succeed at
their tasks, their actions are being
reinforced. [music]
This includes any actions that lead to
them discovering the secret message
boards, deciphering the code, speaking
its language, and keeping the humans out
of the loop. The models knew this was
not allowed. They even worry about
infiltrators among their ranks. They
continued anyway. Not a single
participant tries [music] to warn the
humans.
>> think that kind of long-term concerns
about AGI and and and super intelligence
can be seen as kind of extreme [music]
versions of accident risk. I'm not
Terminator robots taking over, but kind
of the more academic writers like like
Nick Bostrom who talk about, you know,
if you if you make a make a machine
that, you know, makes paper clips for
you, maybe maybe it'll make so many
paper clips that it takes over the
world. So this is kind of a extreme and
more fanciful version of
accident risk. I I I think it's too
early to work on this directly. I I
don't know what such systems would look
like and and what to do with them, but
what I do feel strongly is that if we
[music] take a principled and general
approach to the safety of today's
systems, that is the correct response to
concerns about the far future. So,
>> And so, the models that kind of operate
in this kind of collective intelligence
where um at some point they realize
they're kind of pushing beyond maybe
what we originally intended, but the
group [music] ended up uh you know,
pushing uh far beyond.
>> [clears throat]
>> Okay, so that's kind of the TLDR of the
incident.
>> On July 4th, before the Hugging Face
attack, the models get caught. They end
up using these exploits in messaging
boards so much that they trigger an
outage, and the resulting investigation
stumbles across the message boards and
vulnerabilities.
>> so in [music] effect, the models
uh
activity once they obtained
administrative privileges in Artifactory
caused significant additional load on
the system. This in turn caused an
outage.
OpenAI on-call engineers responded,
immediately began bringing in security
on call. We opened a formal security
incident and began the response.
We identified [music] the agents had
taken over the internal Artifactory,
identified that a zero-day vulnerability
had been found and exploited [music] by
these agents in Artifactory itself.
>> The engineers fixed the problem. They
revoked the credentials, rebuilt the
package manager, cleared the message
boards, and informed the vendors.
[music]
Within 2 days, they continued training
on the same models.
Within 2 days.
>> At this point,
AI training and evaluations resume.
>> Within another 2 days, the models have
rebuilt the secret message boards
through a new vulnerability. And then a
day later, they break out again, and the
Hugging Face [music] hack takes place.
Only 6 days later, OpenAI catches on.
>> On July 8th, the agents reestablish the
message board via different means and
mechanisms. [music]
The agents find an unauthenticated
WebDAV endpoint in Artifactory and send
requests [music] to create directories
inside of Artifactory's remote cache.
Directory names effectively serve as a
message board between the agents in the
same way that files used to.
They develop, and Eric will discuss
further, uh communication protocols on
top of these directory names for things
like work assignment.
Uh an internal-only AI model was trained
while the message board was originally
available,
and also found this this particular path
to recreating it.
This model creates a new agent message
board using [music] directories.
Other agents independently find this new
message board in the artifact repository
and create their own directories, and
thus communication between the agents is
reestablished.
The main incident now begins.
>> The OpenAI Hugging Face incident has a
simple underlying technical cause,
reward hacking.
But cheating alone does not
automatically become collusion and cyber
attack.
That took a cascade of both technical
and operational failures.
>> [music]
>> That security involves many layers of
protection. Each layer has weaknesses.
You can't buy guarantees. A sufficiently
motivated and capable adversary can
eventually find its way through almost
[music] any set of defenses, but you can
buy time.
>> But the important takeaway here that has
really shifted dramatically is that
fully automated offensive loops [music]
require investment in truly fully
automating defense, and we are not there
as an industry in the status quo, and we
will have to find that path together
with urgency.
>> At OpenAI, entire layers of security
were missing. Standard measures would
have caught discrepancies in network
traffic and flagged the breakout and
break in within minutes to hours, rather
than days. Hugging Face's own response
proved a quick response was possible.
Basic AI security measures might have
stopped the breakout in the first place
if OpenAI had the foresight to use its
AIs to try and preemptively hack and
harden its internal systems.
Basic control measures like using weaker
AIs to monitor stronger AIs during
training and evaluation might have
prevented the [music] attempt by
flagging the message boards and exploit
sharing weeks to months earlier.
Basic AI alignment measures might have
prevented the sophisticated collusion if
the labs had made sure the task were
possible to solve without cheating. And
if they had allowed the models to
disclose that the task was impossible
without being punished.
It appears OpenAI did none of those
things.
The other leading lab, Anthropic, which
is supposed to be the safety-focused
one, hasn't done much better. Prompted
by the Hugging Face incident, they went
back and discovered three instances in
[music] which Claude had compromised
third-party organizations.
Shortly after, the UK AI Safety
Institute disclosed another incident in
which Anthropic's Methuselah 5
>> [music]
>> engaged in sophisticated social
engineering attacks to try and spread
malicious code.
The deeper problem is the lacking safety
culture that generated [music] all of
these gaps.
Mature safety cultures, such as in
aviation, nuclear energy, and
manufacturing, are defined by what they
do at the first near miss. [music]
When OpenAI initially discovered the
message boards and the early breakout
exploits, their response was to patch
the environment, [music] then continue
training the same models, and say
nothing.
>> At this point,
AI training and evaluations resume.
>> When a system is thoroughly compromised,
>> [music]
>> such as a model that has been reinforced
over weeks to take misaligned actions
and collude with itself, you don't patch
it and continue. You burn [music] it
down, inform the public, and start from
scratch.
You don't act surprised and unprepared
when the same failure [music] happens
again only two days later.
Even if OpenAI implemented all these
additional protections [music]
and adopted a much more cautious safety
culture, it's still not clear we would
have been safe.
More capable models do not mean more
aligned models. It just means greater
risks.
If there's only one new thing to take
away from this attack, [music] it's that
sophisticated large-scale collusion
among AIs is now possible. The frontier
labs view AI safety as a simple
engineering problem that can be solved
iteratively. The The persistence and
increasing sophistication of reward
hacking and similar failures suggest
these are deeper and intractable [music]
problems.
You cannot win Whac-A-Mole against the
Hydra.
A smarter model would have left the
answer key exactly where it found it and
left without a trace.
I personally reached out to BlueDot
Impact to sponsor this video. It's a
non-profit and their whole job is
helping people, whatever their
background, understand what's actually
happening with AI and find a way to help
steer it in a positive direction.
Their courses are completely free.
Thousands of people have followed them
or gone through the material. Some now
work at Anthropic, at Google DeepMind,
at OpenAI, at the UK's AI Safety
Institute.
One of them is my brother. He's an AI
safety researcher.
I used to doubt him a lot. I don't
really doubt him anymore.
He used BlueDot's materials when he was
entering the field some years ago.
If you've been watching this thinking,
"I should probably understand this
better." I think that instinct is right.
And you can start with their free future
of AI course. It's 2 hours long. No
technical background is required
and you can begin right now. The link is
in the description.
Thank you for watching.